{
  "isTheory": true,
  "openingRemarks": "Use quadratic equation formula to solve these quadratic equations. NB: Quadratic equations are equations of the form \\(ax^2 + bx + c = 0\\) where \\(a \\ne 0\\)",
  "questions": [
    {
        "question": "\\(4 x^{2}-33 x+35=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = -33 and c = 35\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n 4 x^{2}-33 x+35&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-(-33) \\pm \\sqrt{(-33)^{2}-4(4)(35)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{33 \\pm \\sqrt{1089-560}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{33 \\pm \\sqrt{529}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{33 \\pm 23}{8}\\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{33+23}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{56}{8} \\\\\n&=7\\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{33-23}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{10}{8}\\\\\n&=\\frac{5}{4}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{5}{4}\\), \\(-7\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4}\\), \\(-7\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4}\\), \\(7\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{5}{4}\\), \\(7\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5 x^{2}-21 x+4=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 5, b = -21 and c = 4\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}-21 x+4&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\ \n&=\\frac{-(-21) \\pm \\sqrt{(-21)^{2}-4(5)(4)}}{2(5)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{21 \\pm \\sqrt{441-80}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{21 \\pm \\sqrt{361}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{21 \\pm 19}{10} \\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{21+19}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{40}{10}\\\\\n&=4 \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{21-19}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{2}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{1}{5}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(4\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(4\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(-4\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(-4\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5 x^{2}-26 x+5=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 5, b = -26 and c = 5\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}-26 x+5&=0\\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-(-26) \\pm \\sqrt{(-26)^{2}-4(5)(5)}}{2(5)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{26 \\pm \\sqrt{676-100}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{26 \\pm \\sqrt{576}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{26 \\pm 24}{10} \\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{26+24}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{50}{10} \\\\\n&=5 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{26-24}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{2}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{1}{5}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(-5\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(5\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(-5\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(5\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5 x^{2}-50 x+45=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 5, b = -50 and c = 45\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}-50 x+45&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-(-50) \\pm \\sqrt{(-50)^{2}-4(5)(45)}}{2(5)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{50 \\pm \\sqrt{2500-900}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{50 \\pm \\sqrt{1600}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{50 \\pm 40}{10} \\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{50+40}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{90}{10} \\\\\n&=9\\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{50-40}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{50-40}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{10}{10} \\\\\n&=1\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-1\\), \\(-9\\)",
          "\\(-1\\), \\(9\\)",
          "\\(1\\), \\(9\\)",
          "\\(1\\), \\(-9\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(8x + 10x + 3 = 0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 8, b = 10 and c = 3\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8x + 10x + 3 &= 0\\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-10 \\pm \\sqrt{10^{2}-4(8)(3)}}{2(8)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-10 \\pm \\sqrt{100-96}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-10 \\pm \\sqrt{4}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-10 \\pm 2}{16}\\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{-10+2}{16}\\\\\n&=\\frac{-8}{16} \\\\\n&=-\\frac{1}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{-10-2}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-10-2}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-12}{16} \\\\\n&=-\\frac{3}{4}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(8 x^{2}+18 x+9=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 8, b = 18 and c = 9\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8 x^{2}+18 x+9&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-18 \\pm \\sqrt{18^{2}-4(8)(9)}}{2(8)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-18 \\pm \\sqrt{324-288}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-18 \\pm \\sqrt{36}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-18 \\pm 6}{16} \\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{-18-6}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-24}{16}\\\\\n&=-\\frac{3}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{-18+6}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-12}{16} \\\\\n&=-\\frac{3}{4}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(4 x^{2}-8 x-5=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = -8 and c = -5\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4 x^{2}-8 x-5&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-(-8) \\pm \\sqrt{(-8)^{2}-4(4)(-5)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{8 \\pm \\sqrt{64+80}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{8 \\pm \\sqrt{144}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{8 \\pm 12}{8} \\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{8+12}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{20}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{5}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{8-12}{8} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-4}{8} \\\\\n&=-\\frac{1}{2} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{5}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{5}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(8 x^{2}-18 x-5=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 8, b = -18 and c = -5\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8 x^{2}-18 x-5&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4a c}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-(-18) \\pm \\sqrt{(-18)^{2}-4(8)(-5)}}{2(8)} \\\\\n&=\\frac{18 \\pm \\sqrt{324+160}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{18 \\pm \\sqrt{484}}{16}\\\\\n&=\\frac{18 \\pm 22}{16} \\\\\nx_1&=\\frac{18+22}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{40}{16}\\\\\n&=\\frac{5}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{18 -22}{16} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-4}{16}\\\\\n&=-\\frac{1}{4} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(10x^{2}+11 x+3=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 10, b = 11 and c = 3\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10x^{2}+11 x+3&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-11 \\pm \\sqrt{11^{2}-4(10)(3)}}{2(10)} \\\\\n&=-11 \\pm \\dfrac{\\sqrt{121-120}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-11 \\pm \\sqrt{1}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-11 \\pm 1}{20} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-11+1}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-10}{20}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-11-1}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-12}{20} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}+11 x+3 \\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)^{2}+11\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)+3 \\\\\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)-\\dfrac{11}{2}+3 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{5}{2}-\\dfrac{5}{2} \\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}+11 x+3 \\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)^{2}+11\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)+3 \\\\\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{9}{25}\\right)-\\dfrac{33}{5}+3 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{18}{5}-\\dfrac{18}{5} \\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(10x^{2}-31 x+15=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 10, b = -31 and c = 15\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10x^{2}-31 x+15&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-31) \\pm \\sqrt{(-31)^{2}-4(10)(15)}}{2(10)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{31 \\pm \\sqrt{961-600}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{31 \\pm \\sqrt{361}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{31 \\pm 19}{20} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{31+19}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{50}{20}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{5}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{31-19}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{12}{20}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{3}{5} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}-31 x+15 \\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{5}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\right)^{2}-31\\left(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\right)+15 \\\\\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{25}{4}\\right)-\\dfrac{155}{2}+15 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{125}{2}-\\dfrac{125}{2}\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}-31 x+15 \\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{3}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)^{2}-31\\left(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)+15 \\\\\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{9}{25}\\right)-\\dfrac{93}{5}+15 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{18}{5} - \\dfrac{18}{5}\\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(8x^{2}-6x+1=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 8, b = -6 and c = 1\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8x^{2}-6x+1&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-6) \\pm \\sqrt{(-6)^{2}-4(8)(1)}}{2(8)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6 \\pm \\sqrt{36-32}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6 \\pm \\sqrt{4}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6 \\pm 2}{16} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{6+2}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{8}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{6 - 2}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{4} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 8x^{2}-6x+1 \\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{1}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)^{2}-6\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)+1 \\\\\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)-3+1 \\\\\n&=2-2 \\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 8x^{2}-6x+1 \\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{1}{4} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)^{2}-6\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)+1 \\\\\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{16}\\right)-\\dfrac{3}{2}+1 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{2}-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(8x^{2}-14x+3=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 8, b = -14 and c = 3\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8x^{2}-14x+3&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-14) \\pm \\sqrt{(-14)^{2}-4(8)(3)}}{2(8)} \\\\\n&=14 \\pm \\dfrac{\\sqrt{196-96}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{14 \\pm \\sqrt{100}}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{14 \\pm 10}{16} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{14+10}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{24}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{3}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{14-10}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4}{16} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{4} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 0 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 8x^{2}-14x+3 \\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{3}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\right)^{2}-14\\left(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\right)+3 \\\\\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{9}{4}\\right)-21+3 \\\\\n&=18-18 \\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 8x^{2}-14x+3 \\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{1}{4} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)^{2}-14\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)+3 \\\\\n&=8\\left(\\dfrac{1}{16}\\right)-\\dfrac{7}{2}+3 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{2}-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\\\\n&=0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      }, {
        "question": "\\(4x^{2}+19x=-12\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}+19x&=-12 \\\\\n4x^{2}+19 x+12&=0 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = 19 and c = 12\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}+19 x+12&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(19) \\pm \\sqrt{(19)^{2}-4(4)(12)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-19 \\pm \\sqrt{361-192}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-19 \\pm \\sqrt{169}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-19 \\pm 13}{8} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-19+13}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6}{8}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{3}{4} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-19-13}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-32}{8}\\\\\n&=-4 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = -12 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4 x^{2}+19x \\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{3}{4} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4\\left(\\dfrac{-3}{4}\\right)^{2}+19\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\right)\\\\\n&=4\\left(\\dfrac{9}{16}\\right)-\\dfrac{57}{4}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{4}-\\dfrac{57}{4}\\\\\n&=-12\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 4x^{2}+19x\\) if \\(x=-4 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=4(-4)^{2}+19(-4) \\\\\n&=4(16)-76 \\\\\n&=64-76\\\\\n&=-12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\), \\(-4\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\), \\(4\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{4}\\), \\(4\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4}\\), \\(-4\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5 x^{2}+8 x=-3\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}+8 x&=-3 \\\\\n5 x^{2}+8 x+3&=0 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 5, b = 8 and c = 3\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}+8 x+3&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-8 \\pm \\sqrt{8^{2}-4(5)(3)}}{2(5)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-8 \\pm \\sqrt{64-60}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-8 \\pm \\sqrt{4}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-8 \\pm 2}{10} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-8+2}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6}{10} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-8-2}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-10}{10} \\\\\n&=-1 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = -3 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 5 x^{2}+8 x \\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)^{2}+8\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right) \\\\\n&=5\\left(\\dfrac{9}{25}\\right)-\\dfrac{24}{5} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{5}-\\dfrac{24}{5} \\\\\n&=-3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 5 x^{2}+8 x \\) if \\(x=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(-1)^{2}+8(-1) \\\\\n&=5(1)-8 \\\\\n&=5-8 \\\\\n&=-3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(1\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(1\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-1\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-1\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5 x^{2}=27 x+18\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}&=27 x+18 \\\\\n5 x^{2}-27 x-18&=0 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 5, b = -27 and c = -18\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 x^{2}-27 x-18&=0 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-27) \\pm \\sqrt{(-27)^{2}-4(5)(-18)}}{2(5)} \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{27 \\pm \\sqrt{729+360}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{27 \\pm \\sqrt{1089}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{27 \\pm 33}{10} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{27+33}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{60}{10} \\\\\n&=6 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{27-33}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6}{10} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 5 x^{2}\\) if \\(x=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5(6)^{2} \\\\\n&=5(36)\\\\\n&=180 \\\\ \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 27x+18\\) if \\(x=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=27(6)+18 \\\\\n&=162+18 \\\\\n&=180\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 5 x^{2}\\) if \\( x=-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=5\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)^{2} \\\\\n&=5\\left(\\dfrac{9}{25}\\right) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{5}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 27x+18\\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{3}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=27\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\right)+18 \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{81}{5}+18\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{5}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(6\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(6\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-6\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{3}{5}\\), \\(-6\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(10 x^{2}=3x+1\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10 x^{2}&=3x+1 \\\\ \n10 x^{2}-3x-1&=0 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 10, b = -3 and c = -1\\[\n\\begin{align*} \n10 x^{2}-3x-1&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-3) \\pm \\sqrt{(-3)^{2}-4(10)(-1)}}{2(10)} \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{3 \\pm \\sqrt{9+40}}{20} \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{3 \\pm \\sqrt{49}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{3 \\pm 7}{20}\\\\ \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{3+7}{20} \\\\ \n&=\\frac{10}{20} \\\\ \n&=\\frac{1}{2} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{3-7}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-4}{20}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}\\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{1}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\right)^{2} \\\\ \n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{1}{25}\\right)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{2}{5}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x+1\\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{1}{5} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\right)+1 \\\\ \n&=-\\dfrac{3}{5}+1 \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{2}{5}\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}\\) if \\( x=\\dfrac{1}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)^{2}\\\\\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right) \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{5}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 3x+1\\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{1}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=3\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)+1 \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{3}{2}+1\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{5}{2}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5}\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(10 x^{2}=25 x+15\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10 x^{2}&=25 x+15 \\\\\n10 x^{2}-25 x-15&=0 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 10, b = -25 and c = -15\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10 x^{2}-25 x-15&=0 \\\\ \nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{(-25) \\pm \\sqrt{(-25)^{2}-4(10)(-15)}}{2(10)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{25 \\pm \\sqrt{625+600}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{25 \\pm \\sqrt{1225}}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{25 \\pm 35}{20} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{25+35}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{60}{20}\\\\\n&=3 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{25-35}{20} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-10}{20}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}\\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)^{2} \\\\\n&=10\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right) \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{5}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2x+15\\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{1}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=25\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)+15 \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{25}{2}+15 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{5}{2} \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 10 x^{2}\\) if \\( x=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=10(3)^{2} \\\\\n&=10(9) \\\\\n& =90\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 25x+15\\) if \\(x=3 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=25(3)+15 \\\\\n&=75+15 \\\\\n&=90 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(3\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-3\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-3\\), \\(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)",
          "\\(3\\), \\(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(2 x^{2}=9(x+2)\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2 x^{2}&=9(x+2) \\\\\n2 x^{2}&=9 x+18 \\\\\n2 x^{2}-9 x-18&=0 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a=2, d b=-9,  c=-18\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2 x^{2}-9 x-18&=0 \\\\ \nx_1,x_2&=-b \\pm \\dfrac{\\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-9) \\pm \\sqrt{(-9)^{2}-4(2)(-18)}}{2(2)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9 \\pm \\sqrt{81+144}}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9 \\pm \\sqrt{225}}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9 \\pm 15}{4} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{9+15}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{24}{4}\\\\\n&=6 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{9-15}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6}{4}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2x^{2}\\) if \\(x=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2(6)^{2} \\\\\n&=2(36)\\\\\n&=72\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 9(x+2)\\) if \\(x=6 \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=9(6+2) \\\\\n&=9(8)\\\\\n&=72\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 2x^{2}\\) if \\(x=-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=2\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\right)^{2} \\\\\n&=2\\left(\\dfrac{9}{4}\\right)\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{2}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( 9(x+2)\\) if \\( x=-\\dfrac{3}{2} \\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=9\\left(-\\dfrac{3}{2}+2\\right) \\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{27}{2}+18 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{9}{2}\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-6\\), \\(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
          "\\(6\\), \\(-\\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
          "\\(6\\), \\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
          "\\(-6\\), \\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\((4 x+3)(x+3)=13\\)",
        "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n(4 x+3)(x+3)&=13 \\\\\n4 x^{2}+12 x+3 x+9&=13 \\\\\n4 x^{2}+12 x+3 x+9-13&=0 \\\\\n4 x^{2}+15 x-4&=0 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = 15 and c = -4\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4 x^{2}+15 x-4&=0 \\\\ \nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4 a c}}{2 a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-15 \\pm \\sqrt{(15)^{2}-4(4)(-4)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-15 \\pm \\sqrt{225+64}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-15 \\pm \\sqrt{289}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-15 \\pm 17}{8} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-15+17}{8} \\\\ \n&=\\dfrac{2}{8}\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{1}{4} \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-15-17}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-32}{8}\\\\\n&=-4  \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Check LHS = 13 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\( (4 x+3)(x+3)\\) if \\(x=\\dfrac{1}{4}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=\\left(4\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\right)+3\\right)\\left(\\dfrac{1}{4}+3\\right) \\\\\n&=(1+3)\\left(\\dfrac{13}{4}\\right) \\\\\n&=(4)\\left(\\dfrac{13}{4}\\right) \\\\\n&=13\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n<div>Evaluate \\( (4 x+3)(x+3)\\) if \\(x=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n&=(4(-4)+3)(-4+3) \\\\\n&=(-16+3)(-1) \\\\\n&=(-13)(-1) \\\\\n&=13\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(4\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(-4\\)",
          "\\(-\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(4\\)",
          "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4}\\), \\(-4\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(2x^{2}+2x-6=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 2, b = 2 and c = -6\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2x^{2}+2x-6&=0 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-2 \\pm \\sqrt{2^{2}-4(2)(-6)}}{2(2)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-2 \\pm \\sqrt{4+48}}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-2 \\pm \\sqrt{52}}{4} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-2 \\pm 7.21}{4} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-2+7.21}{4} \\\\\n&=1.30 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-2-7.21}{4} \\\\\n&=-2.30 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-2.30\\), \\(1.30\\)",
          "\\(-2.30\\), \\(-1.30\\)",
          "\\(2.30\\), \\(-1.30\\)",
          "\\(2.30\\), \\(1.30\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(x^{2}+4 x-2=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 1, b = 4 and c = -2\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx^{2}+4 x-2&=0 \\\\\nx=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\nx=\\dfrac{-4 \\pm \\sqrt{4^{2}-4(1)(-2)}}{2(1)} \\\\\nx=\\dfrac{-4 \\pm \\sqrt{16+8}}{2} \\\\\nx=\\dfrac{-4 \\pm \\sqrt{24}}{2} \\\\\nx=\\dfrac{-4+4.90}{2} \\\\\nx=0.50 \\\\ \\\\\nx=\\dfrac{-4-4.90}{2} \\\\\nx=-4.50 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-1.45\\), \\(-2.95\\)",
          "\\(-1.95\\), \\(2.95\\)",
          "\\(0.50\\), \\(-4.50\\)",
          "\\(1.95\\), \\(2.95\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(3x^{2}-4x-3=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 3, b = -4 and c = -3\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x^{2}-4x-3&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{(-4) \\pm \\sqrt{(-4)^{2}-4(3)(-3)}}{2(3)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4 \\pm \\sqrt{16+36}}{6} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4 \\pm \\sqrt{52}}{6} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{4 \\pm 7.21}{6} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{4+7.21}{6} \\\\\n&=1.87\\\\ \\\\\nx_2& =\\dfrac{4-7.21}{6} \\\\\n&=-0.54\\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-0.54\\), \\(-1.87\\)",
          "\\(-0.54\\), \\(1.87\\)",
          "\\(0.54\\), \\(1.87\\)",
          "\\(0.54\\), \\(-1.87\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(4x^{2}+x-6=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = 1 and c = -6\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}+x-6&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{1^{2}-4(4)(-6)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{1+96}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{97}}{8} \\\\ \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm 9.85}{8} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-1+9.85}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{8.85}{8}\\\\\n&=1.11 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-1-9.85}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-10.85}{8} \\\\\n&=-1.36 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-1.11\\), \\(-1.36\\)",
          "\\(1.11\\), \\(1.36\\)",
          "\\(-1.11\\), \\(1.36\\)",
          "\\(-1.36\\), \\(1.11\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(3x^{2}+x-5=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 3, b = 1 and c = -5\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x^{2}+x-5&=0\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{1^{2}-4(3)(-5)}}{2(3)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{1+60}}{6} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{61}}{6} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm 7.81}{6} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-1+7.81}{6} \\\\\n&=1.14 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-1-7.81}{6} \\\\\n&=-1.47 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-1.47\\), \\(1.14\\)",
          "\\(-1.47\\), \\(-1.14\\)",
          "\\(1.47\\), \\(1.14\\)",
          "\\(1.47\\), \\(-1.14\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(4x^{2}+5 x-7=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = 5 and c = -7\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}+5 x-7&=0 \\\\\nx_1, x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-5 \\pm \\sqrt{5^{2}-4(4)(-7)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-5 \\pm \\sqrt{25+112}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-5 \\pm \\sqrt{137}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-5 \\pm 11.71}{8} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-5+11.71}{8} \\\\\n&=0.84 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-5-11.71}{8} \\\\\n&=-2.09 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-2.09\\), \\(0.84\\)",
          "\\(-2.09\\), \\(-0.84\\)",
          "\\(2.09\\), \\(0.84\\)",
          "\\(2.09\\), \\(-0.84\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5x^{2}+x-6=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 5, b = 1 and c = -6\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5x^{2}+x-6&=0 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{1^{2}-4(5)(-6)}}{2(5)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{1+120}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-1 \\pm \\sqrt{121}}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1 \\pm 11}{10} \\\\\\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1+11}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{10}{10} \\\\\n&=1 \\\\ \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-1-11}{10} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-12}{10}\\\\\n&=-\\dfrac{6}{5} \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-1\\), \\(-\\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
          "\\(1\\), \\(\\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
          "\\(-1\\), \\(\\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
          "\\(1\\), \\(-\\dfrac{6}{5}\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(4x^{2}+6 x-1=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = 6 and c = -1\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}+6 x-1&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\frac{-6 \\pm \\sqrt{6^{2}-4(4)(-1)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm \\sqrt{36+16}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm \\sqrt{52}}{8} \\\\&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm 7.21}{8} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-6+7.21}{8} \\\\\n&=0.15 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\frac{-6-7.21}{8} \\\\\n&=-1.65 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-1.65\\), \\(-0.15\\)",
          "\\(-1.65\\), \\(0.15\\)",
          "\\(1.65\\), \\(0.15\\)",
          "\\(1.65\\), \\(-0.15\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(4x^{2}-6 x+1=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = -6 and c = 1\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}-6 x+1&=0 \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-(-6) \\pm \\sqrt{(-6)^{2}-4(4)(1)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6 \\pm \\sqrt{36-16}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6 \\pm \\sqrt{20}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{6 \\pm 4.47}{8} \\\\\\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{6+4.47}{8} \\\\\n&=1.31 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{6-4.47}{8} \\\\\n&=0.19 \\\\ \n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(0.19\\), \\(1.31\\)",
          "\\(-0.19\\), \\(1.31\\)",
          "\\(-0.19\\), \\(-1.31\\)",
          "\\(0.19\\), \\(-1.31\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(4x^{2}+6 x-3=0\\)",
        "answer": "<p>Compared to general form of quadratic equation, a = 4, b = 6 and c = -3\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x^{2}+6 x-3&=0 \\\\\nx_1,x_2&=\\dfrac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm \\sqrt{6^{2}-4(4)(-3)}}{2(4)} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm \\sqrt{36+48}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm \\sqrt{84}}{8} \\\\\n&=\\dfrac{-6 \\pm 9.17}{8} \\\\\nx_1&=\\dfrac{-6+9.17}{8} \\\\\n&=0.40 \\\\ \\\\\nx_2&=\\dfrac{-6-9.17}{8} \\\\ \n&=-1.90\\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\] \n\n",
        "choices": [
          "\\(-0.40\\), \\(-1.90\\)",
          "\\(0.40\\), \\(1.90\\)",
          "\\(-0.40\\), \\(1.90\\)",
          "\\(0.40\\), \\(-1.90\\)"
        ],
        "correctChoice": 3
      }
  ]
}
